7waystointernetriches.com 2010-12-12

# www.7waystointernetriches.com - Privacy Policy

**7waystointernetriches.com  and all related Websites**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**7waystointernetriches.com** , (7WTIR) is committed to protecting the privacy of all individuals who provide their personal information. 7WTIR does not collect, use or disclose the personal information of individuals without their knowledge and consent.

It is 7WTIR'S policy to comply with the privacy legislation within each jurisdiction in which we operate. Sometimes the privacy legislation and / or an individual's right to privacy are different from one jurisdiction to another.

This policy describes the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of 7WTIR and applies to 7WTIR'S collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by 7WTIR on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies and websites (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various Third Party websites, and (c) to 7WTIR's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from Third Parties. 7WTIR is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of Third Party websites or applications.

**By visiting this website and requesting information, products or services, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not provide any information or use any of the services or products offered or provided on any of the websites referred to in this Privacy Policy.**

**Please Note: 7WTIR from time to time, may make changes to this privacy policy to reflect changes in its legal or regulatory obligations or in the manner in which we deal with your personal information. Changes are effective upon posting. It is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. We do not provide notices of changes in any manner other than by positing the changes at this web site. We encourage you to refer back to this policy on a regular basis.**

Last updated: September 10, 2009

**THE INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND DISSEMINATION PRACTICES OF 7WTIR.**

**1\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

**1.1 Survey Information**

7WTIR collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes a survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by Third Parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, 7WTIR or a Third Party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to 7WTIR, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, postal/zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social insurance/security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). 7WTIR may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this web site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to 7WTIR or Third Party.

**1.2 Site Membership or Registration**

To the extent registration is required to receive email and possibly postal communications from 7WTIR, this Privacy Policy also applies to consumers that have agreed to receive e-mail marketing from 7WTIR, whether at our Website, via email, on Third Party websites or otherwise. We collect information in certain portions of our Website, where guests provide content submissions and suggestions or participate in interactive online activities (i.e., by way of responding to questions and surveys, community listings, ratings, searches and comparison searches, bidding, purchasing, chat, games, or bulletin boards, etc.). The personal profile information you submit to 7WTIR remains your property, but by submitting that information to 7WTIR, you grant 7WTIR, the right to use that information for marketing purposes. 7WTIR may also use such information for content improvement and feedback purposes. We may sell the personal information that you supply to us and we may join together with other businesses to bring selected retail opportunities to our members. These businesses may include providers of direct marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. In addition, 7WTIR reserves the right to release current or past member information in the event 7WTIR believes that the membership is being or has been used in violation of the Rules or to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if 7WTIR is sold or acquired, or when 7WTIR deems it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, you hereby consent to disclosure of any record or communication to any Third Party when 7WTIR, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate

"Subscription" occurs when an end-user registers for 7WTIR's services, either via registration at our website, via co-registration at a marketing partner's website, or via a permission pass / opt-out / no-opt mailing. 7WTIR collects personally identifiable information about our subscribers, based on: information gathered at the time of registration, subscriber interaction and response to subsequent electronic mailings and website use, information provided by marketing partners, and information appended from data aggregators. Information collected may include, but is not necessarily limited to: name, email address, postal address, gender, birth date, telephone number, activity, interests, user behavior and other demographic information. This information enables us to better tailor our content to subscribers' needs and to help our clients to promote and sell their products and services.

**1.3 Third Party List Information**

7WTIR collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and 7WTIR subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, postal/zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, 7WTIR seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to 7WTIR and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from Advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

**1.4 Other Information**

Other occasions when 7WTIR obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by 7WTIR or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through 7WTIR's customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a 7WTIR service or newsletter (together, "Other Information").

**1.5 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology**

7WTIR currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, 7WTIR may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information").

**a) Cookies**  
A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows 7WTIR to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in 7WTIR's database. You may read more about cookies at [cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). Individuals who use the Websites need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Websites.

**b) Web Beacons**  
A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (see http://truste.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows 7WTIR to track certain websites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, 7WTIR also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in 7WTIR's database.

**c) New Technology**  
The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is 7WTIR's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, 7WTIR strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

**d) Usage Tracking**  
7WTIR tracks information related to the electronic mailings and web pages viewed by users and subscribers, as well as the hyperlinks clicked by subscribers, while viewing our emails or visiting our websites.

**e) Log Files**  
Log files are used to track and monitor subscriber usage

**f) Optional Registration**  
7WTIR may offer free voluntary registration to potential subscribers. During such registration, the subscriber is required to supply an email address and other personal information. This information is required if the subscriber wants to participate in Company services.

**g) Feedback and Inquiries**  
You have the ability to contact 7WTIR to provide us with their feedback. 7WTIR uses this information to respond to you and analyze customer service issues.

**1.6 Outside Information**

7WTIR may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of 7WTIR including information located in public databases ("Outside Information").

**1.7 Individual Information**

As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information 7WTIR gathers or receives about individuals.

**1.8 No Information Collected from Children**

7WTIR will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If 7WTIR obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, 7WTIR has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. 7WTIR has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

**1.9 Credit Card Information**

7WTIR may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from 7WTIR. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to 7WTIR, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. 7WTIR will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

**1.10 Links to External Websites**

7WTIR's emails and websites may contain links to external websites. You will be taken to external websites if you click on these links. Your information may be passed from 7WTIR's database to the external website, and/or external database, for your convenience (e.g. your information may be used to pre-fill a form at a destination website). 7WTIR is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any external website owner. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website you visit.

**2\. USE OF INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION**

**2.1 Discretion to Use Information**

7WTIR MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION.

The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how 7WTIR currently uses Individual Information, but 7WTIR may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted above, 7WTIR may update this policy from time to time. 7WTIR may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

**2.2 Email and Unsubscribe Policy**

7WTIR uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. 7WTIR may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all 7WTIR's email lists, use this unsubscribe Link <http://www.ewimail.com/unsubscribe.aspx> 

7WTIR's unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by 7WTIR on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of Third Parties and your personal information may still be shared with Third Parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.

You should also note that unsubscribing from 7WTIR's electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the subscriber's information from any Third Party associates and licensees of the data. Since Third Party associates and licensee partners maintain separate databases from 7WTIR, and you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

**2.3 Content of Email Messages**

In certain commercial email messages sent by or for 7WTIR, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line, but hitting the "Reply" button will not cause a reply email to be sent to 7WTIR. The "Subject:" line of 7WTIR email messages will usually contain a line provided from the Advertiser to 7WTIR.

**2.4 Solicited Email**

7WTIR only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from 7WTIR or to individuals who have agreed on Third Party websites to receive email from Third Parties such as 7WTIR. 7WTIR does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to 7WTIR S email messages.

**2.5 Targeted Advertising**

7WTIR uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, 7WTIR uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.7 below) to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and 7WTIR attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. 7WTIR may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

**2.6 Direct Mail and Telemarketing**

7WTIR may use Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones.

**2.7 Use of Technology Information**

7WTIR uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of 7WTIR's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps 7WTIR to better understand the online habits of individuals so that 7WTIR can target advertising and promotions to them.

**2.8 Profiles of Individuals**

7WTIR uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

**2.9 Storage of Individual Information**

7WTIR stores the Individual Information in a database on its computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under 7WTIR's control. Not withstanding such measures, 7WTIR cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

**3\. DISSEMINATION OF INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION**

**3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties**

7WTIR MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN 7WTIR'S SOLE DISCRETION.

**3.2 Order Fulfillment**

7WTIR will transfer Individual Information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such Third Party while using 7WTIR's websites or when responding to offers provided by 7WTIR.

**3.3 Legal Process**

7WTIR may disclose Individual Information as permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements, and/or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.

**3.4 Summary Data**

7WTIR may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.

**3.5 Access**

Individuals are entitled to access to their personal information which is in the possession of 7WTIR. If an individual wants to see their personal information, they may contact the Privacy Officer. 7WTIR will provide access to personal information (some exceptions might apply) and provide any assistance required in understanding the nature of personal information that is in 7WTIR's possession. There is no cost to gain access to personal information.

7WTIR may ask that the individual put their request in writing. If 7WTIR is unable to give access, 7WTIR will inform the individual within 30 days, in writing, with the reasons for not granting access.

**3.6 Do Not Call Registry Waiver**

Even though you may be on a National or State DO NOT CALL list, by submitting your contact information which may include your telephone number, you are expressly authorizing us and our advertising businesses and affiliates to contact you by telephone at the number you have used regarding the information you have expressed.

**4\. PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THIRD PARTIES**

**4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons**

Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. 7WTIR does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and 7WTIR has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.

**4.2 Links**

The Websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of Third Parties. 7WTIR is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. 7WTIR does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party websites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

**4.3 Affiliated Companies**

7WTIR may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with 7WTIR in 7WTIR's discretion.

**5\. UNSUBSCRIBE PROCEDURES**

If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from 7WTIR, you have several options:

**a) Unsubscribe from one email list** **  
** Unsubscribe Link:

<http://www.ewimail.com/unsubscribe.aspx> 

**b) Unsubscribe from all of 7WTIR's email lists** **  
** We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by 7WTIR. To globally unsubscribe from all of 7WTIR's lists.

Unsubscribe Link:

<http://www.ewimail.com/unsubscribe.aspx> 

**6\. FURTHER INQUIRIES**

Your privacy is important to us. If you have any questions about 7WTIR's Privacy Policy or concerns about the way personal information is being used, please contact our Privacy Officer at:

Privacy Offer 7waystointernetriches.com

5072 N. 300 W.

Provo, UT 84604

800-371-9876

 If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about how we manage your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer by telephone, in writing or by e-mail. If you are not satisfied with our response, you may be entitled to make a written submission to the Privacy Commissioner in your jurisdiction.

**7\. INTERPRETATION OF PRIVACY POLICY**

Any interpretation associated with this Privacy Policy will be made by our Privacy Officer.

This Privacy Policy does not create or confer upon any individual any rights, or impose upon 7WTIR any obligations outside of, or in addition to, any rights or obligations imposed by federal and state privacy laws, as applicable. Should there be, in a specific case, any inconsistency between this Privacy Policy and federal and provincial privacy laws, as applicable, this Privacy Policy shall be interpreted, in respect of that case, to give effect to, and comply with, such privacy laws.
